Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 1 (donated 1990), 1976-1990; Series 1; 82 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1976-1990; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - National Institute Against Prejudice and Violence, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - National Institute for Justice, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - National Institute for Transplant Development,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - The National Journal, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - National Kidney Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - National Lawyers Guild,D.C. Chapter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - National League of Cities (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - National League of Cities (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - National League of Cities (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - National League of Cities Conference,New Orleans, Nov.26-30, 1983 (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - National League of Cities Conference,New Orleans, Nov.26-30, 1983 (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - National League of Cities Conference,New Orleans, Nov.26-30, 1983 (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - National League of Cities Conference,New Orleans, Nov.26-30, 1983 (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - National League of Cities Conference December 1988, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - National League of Cities- F.A.R.E. Committee Conference, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - National League of Cities International Economic Development Task Force, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - National Learning Center / Capital Children's Museum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - National Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - National Moratorium on Prison Construction, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - National Organization foe Adaptive Housing,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - National Organization for Victim Assistance (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - National Organization for Victim Assistance (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - National Park Service, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - National Parking Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - National Political Congress of Black Women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - National Presbyterian Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - National Progressive Citizens Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - National Press Building Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - National Rainbow Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - National Rehabilitation Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - National Rehabilitation Hospital, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - National Retired Teachers Association (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - National Retired Teachers Association (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - National Rifle Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - National Right To Life Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - National Science Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - National Science Technology Week, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - National Sheriffs' Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - National Sorority Phi Delta Kappa,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - National Tots and Teens,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - National Trade Productions,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - National Union Hospital and Health Care Employees, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - National University School of Law, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - National Urban Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - National Urban League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - National Urban / Rural Fellows, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Native Sun and Associates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Native Washington Club,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Nativity Church Rectory, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Nature Conservancy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Naturopathic Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Navy Recruiting District Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Near Northeast Community Improvement Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Neighborhood Development Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Neighborhood Economic Development Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Neighborhood Legal Services Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Neighborhood Planning Council (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Neighborhood Planning Council (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Neighborhood Transportation Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Neighborhood Trying Block Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Neighborhood Watch Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Neighbors of Burns Street Organization, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Neighbors of Harvard Street, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Neighbors,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Nelson Tenants Union, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Netherlands Owners,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - New Beginnings, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - New Bethel Baptist Church (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - New Bethel Baptist Church (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - New Dunbar High School Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - The New Education Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - New Endeavors by Women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 1926 and 1930 New Hampshire, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - The New Home Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - New Image Community Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - New Life,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - The New Macedonia Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - New Merridian Hill Community Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - New Right Watch, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - New Samaritan Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - New Southern Rock Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - The New Theatre of Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - New York Avenue Presbyterian Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - News Release,Re: evictions, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - The Next Step, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Nichiren Shoshu Soka Gakkai of America (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Nichiren Shoshu Soka Gakkai of America (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - 911, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Nineteenth Street Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - 2100 Nineteenth Street Co-op, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Nineteenth Street Playground, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - 1909 Nineteenth Street Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Ninth Street,1900 Block, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - No-Fault Auto Insurance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - Non-Partisan Political Action Association of the District of Columbia,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - North American Chinese Volleyball Tournament, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - North American Theatre Groups,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - North Capitol Neighborhood Development,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - North Capitol Neighborhood Housing, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina A and T University, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - North Dupont Community Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - North Michigan Park Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Northeast Boundary Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Northeast Community Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Northeast Door, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Northeast Employment Services Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Northwest Boundary Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Northwest Settlement House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Notices for Public Hearings, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - NOVA, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Noyes Elementary School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - NS and T Bank, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Freeze Resource Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Nuclear Weapons Freeze, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Advisory Board (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Advisory Board (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Nurse Midwifery, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Nursing Homes, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Oakwood Commons Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Oakwood Mews, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Oakwood Tenants, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - OFEGRO, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Offenders Legal Liberation Movement Organization, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Office of Business and Economic Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Office of Community-Based Residential Facilities, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Office Community Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Office of Criminal Justice Plans and Analysis (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Office of Criminal Justice Plans and Analysis (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Office of Criminal Justice Plans and Analysis (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Office of District of Columbia Auditors, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Office of Drug Control Policy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Office of Management and Budget, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Office Manual (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Office Manual (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Office Manual (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Office Manual (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Office of the Mayor, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Office of People's Council,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Office of Personnel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Office of Planning and Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Office Renovations, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Office of Technology Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Office of Zoning Independence Act of 1989, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Ofeild Dukes and Associates,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Old Asta Theatre, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Older Americans Month, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Older Women's League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Jack Olender and Associates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Olender Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Omega Psi Psi Fraternity,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Omnia Bonia,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - One Fund Drive, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - One Fund Givers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - One Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - One Washington Circle Hotel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Onely,Ethal, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Ontario Lakers (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Ontario Lakers (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Ontario Lakers (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Ontario Lakers (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - 2422 Ontario Road,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Operation Bright Side, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Operation Caribbean Cruise, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Operation Know Thyself, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Operation Support Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Opportunity Funding Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Options,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Organization of African Unity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Organization of Black Metropolitan Police Officials, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Organization of Black Metropolitan Police Officials Annual Breakfast, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Orphan Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - OSAY Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Our Block Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Out!, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Outstanding Young Men of America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Brig Owens and Associates,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Oyster School Community, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Palisades Citizens Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Paralyzed Veterans of America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Paramedic Training Class, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Pardis Italian Gourmet, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Parents and Friends of Lesbian and Gay Men of Washington Metropolitan Area,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Parents United for D.C. Public Schools, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Parents United for Full School Funding, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Parents and Youth Against Drugs and Alcohol, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Parents and Youth on Family Functioning, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Park East Apartment 1845 Summit Place,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Park Ellison Tenants Association,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Park-Monroe Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Park Morton, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Park Regent, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Park Road Community Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Park Road Community Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Park Road Festival, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - 1515 Park Road,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - 1315 Park Road Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - 1451 and 1445 Park Road Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Park Towers Apartment Building, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Parking Fees, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Parkside, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Parole (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Parole (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Partners for Livable Places, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Pathfinder Corporation for International Trade, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Patients Rights Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Pavilion at the Old Post Office, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Peabody-Habson P.T.A., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Peabody Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Peace Child Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Peace Lutheran Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Peagues,Chailerdo K., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Pearson,Charles, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Pearson,Kerry, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Pierce-Warwick Adoption Service, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Pending Legislation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (1 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (2 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (3 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (4 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (5 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (6 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (7 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (8 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (9 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (10 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (11 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (12 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (13 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (14 of 14), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Ethics, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Justice for Janitors Issue, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (1 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (2 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (3 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (4 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (5 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (6 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (7 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Lansburghs Site (Gunwyn) (8 of 8), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square-Federal Triangle Building (Western) (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square-Federal Triangle Building (Western) (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square-Federal Triangle Building (Western) (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square-General (Western), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square Restructuring (Western) (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation- Market Square-Restructuring (Western) (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Peoples Anti-War Mobilization, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 7)